m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Bazinga  猫中之王  12CC醉芝士
校对：风一样的男子赛  疯一样的妹子猫
总监   YY
后期：孤帆    时间轴：贝贝
老爸老妈浪漫史
第八季  第十六集
孩子们  你们可能还记得
Kids, early in this story,
我曾在故事开头说过类似这种话
you may recall me saying something along the lines of...
好了  再也不谈恋爱了
Okay, no more dating.
我已经准备好安定下来
I am ready to settle down.
当时  还真以为自己是发自肺腑的
And at the time, I probably thought I meant it.
不过  孩子们  说实话
But, kids, I'll be honest.
单身真是太欢乐了
Being single's fun.
做为一名纽约的年轻单身汉
As a young unattached man in New York City,
我过得精彩极了
I had a great time.
真心精彩啊
A great time.
说到哪了
What was I saying?
对哦
Oh, yeah.
我过得精彩极了  直到出现一个很特别的人
I had such a great time that it took someone very special
才让我有了安定下来的想法
to make me want to settle down.
而那个特别的人
And that someone...
就是珍妮特
was Jeanette.
珍妮特特别在哪里
What made Jeanette so special? Well...
那是犯规啊
That was a foul!
珍妮特是我遇见你们妈妈之前
Jeanette was the last girl I dated
最后一个女友
before I met your mother.
那女孩最终让我决定
The girl who finally got me to say...
不再恋爱了
>No more dating.
我准备好安定下来了
I'm ready to settle down.
发自肺腑的
...and really mean it.
不过时间先往前倒一点
But let's back up a little bit.
她拿酒瓶砸坏了你的电视机
She broke your TV with a beer bottle?
拿她的话说  她本想砸窗户的
In her defense, she was aiming for the window.
老兄  你得甩了这女的
Dude, you gotta get rid of this girl.
同意  你得在这疯妹妹
Agreed. Cray-cray gotta go bye-bye
拿刀刀捅你前  跟她说拜拜
before you get stab-stabbed.
是吗
Oh, really?
你们这么说
And are you guys saying this
是不希望我和珍妮特在一起
because you don't want me to be with Jeanette,
还是不希望我恢复单身
or because you want me to stay single
好让你们继续塞东西过来啊
so you guys can keep your clubhouse?
我控诉[法语]
J'accuse!
我不是无的放矢  他们也心知肚明
I had a point, and they knew it.
2013年初
You see, in early 2013,
那时就我一人还单着
I was the only single guy in the group.
这就意味着只要马修和巴尼买了
Which meant whenever Marshall or Barney bought something
伴侣不准他们放家里的东西...
they weren't allowed to keep in their apartments...
话说  泰德  这让我想起来
You know what, Ted? That reminds me.
我刚买了个瑞士古董钟
I just bought this antique Swiss clock,
不过罗宾不让放家里
but Robin won't let us put it in the apartment,
于是我就打算放你这了
so I was gonna leave it at your place.
不过有个问题是  它坏了
Only problem? It's broken.
所以我会坐这  试着修好它
So I was just gonna sit here and try to fix it
你也可以顺便说昨晚和珍妮特做了什么
while maybe you tell us what you and Jeanette did last night?
好吧  珍妮特是玛丽莲・梦露的脑残粉
Okay. Well, uh, Jeanette is a big Marilyn Monroe fan.
可以了[听到了吧]  能叫唤了
There you go! Now it's working!
布谷鸟声也可以形容别人白痴  疯子
抱歉  继续说  她是玛丽莲・梦露的粉丝
Sorry. Sorry. Go on. Go on. She's a Marilyn Monroe fan
我猜你俩一起看了她的电影吗
so I guess you watched one of her movies?
没有  我们召唤了她的亡灵
Uh, No, we had a seance.
瞧[听他说的]  跟新的一样
Look at that! Good as new.
然后呢  你们跟异度空间的玛丽莲
Anyway, were you able to contact Marilyn
通上话了吗
in the spirit world?
没  我们跟她的猫通上话了
No. We talked to her cat.
螺丝松了[脑子坏了]  问题找到了
Screw loose! That's the problem.
貌似有人肚子饿了
Looks like somebody's hungry.
我去给他弄吃的
I'm gonna get his food ready.
罗宾  你能把他抱起来吗
Robin, can you grab him?
我能吗  真是求之不得啊
Can I? Try and stop me!
孩子们  莉莉没有意识到
Now, kids, what Lily didn't realize--
其实我们都没意识到
what none of us realized, in fact--
你们的堂兄马文出生了八个月之久
was that in the eight months since your cousin Marvin was born,
罗宾还一次都没抱过他呢
Robin had never once held him.
事实上  她想到抱他就怕
The truth was, the thought of holding him terrified her,
因此她一直在不着痕迹地回避
so she had always avoided it, ever so discreetly.
-你能抱着...  -该死  瞧啊
- Can you hold... - Oh, shoot! Look at that!
天哪
Oh, geez.
我来抱
I got him.
来啊  小乖乖
Come here, you little munchkin.
老兄
Aw, man...
那下次我来
Oh, well, I call next.
我该走了  珍妮特的非常时间到了
Well, I should go. It's time for Jeanette's... something.
珍妮特的什么非常时间  泰德
Time for Jeanette's what, Ted?
我们要带她的狗狗去驱魔人那
Uh, we're taking her dog to an exorcist.
泰德  那听起来...
Wow, Ted, that sounds...
该死[真扯淡]  这回是真坏了
Crap, it's really broken now.
好吧  好吧  我承认  她疯疯癫癫的
Okay, fine. I admit it. She's crazy.
这明摆着的
Obviously.
但我又不是要跟她过一辈子
But I'm not in this for the long haul.
现在只是好玩而已
It's just, you know, it's just fun.
一开始的确好玩
Of course it's fun, at first.
不过在翻云覆雨时  她开始喊她
But then when she starts calling out the name of her
高中理科老师的名字时
high school science teacher in the throes of passion,
就更好玩了
it's really fun.
然后她把刀带到床上
But then when she starts bringing knives into bed
害你为自身安全担惊受怕是
and making you fear for your safety?
那更是好玩到不行啊
It's really, really fun.
再后来她逼你在高速上蒙着眼睛开车时
But then when she starts unbuttoning your pants
还一边要解开你的裤子
while you're being forced to drive blindfolded
并拿枪指着你的...
down the freeway with a gun pointed at your...
不好意思  我们在聊什么来着
I'm sorry, what were we talking about?
珍妮特
Jeanette.
对哦  那女孩是个疯子
Oh, right. That girl's crazy.
你得跟她分手
You gotta break up with her.
我知道  你们是对的  我应该跟她分手
I know. I know. You're right. I-I have to break up with her.
不过我得在公共场合分手
I should do it in a public place, though,
以免她失控
so she doesn't flip out.
于是第二天晚上  我和她约在公共场所
So the next night, I met her in a public place
以免她失控
so she wouldn't flip out.
我要杀了你  裁判
I will kill you, ref!
我要当着这么多人面把你碎尸万段
I will kill you in front of all these people!
老天啊
Oh, boy.
怎么  你以为我在这么多人面前就不敢吗
What, you think I won't just 'cause I'm in a public place?!
老娘豁出去了  下半辈子坐牢也愿意
I'll go to jail for the rest of my life if I have to!
比赛开始前  我想跟你谈谈
Listen, before the game starts, I think we need to talk.
真不敢相信泰德死了
I can't believe Ted's dead.
就是啊
I know.
死得真惨啊
What a way to go.
被火箭筒给爆了
Killed by a bazooka.
行了行了  我心情不好打得差嘛
All right, all right, so I'm not on my game today.
我昨晚刚跟人分手嘛
I did just break up with someone last night.
总之
Anyway...
我出去溜达一会
I gotta hop out for a bit.
你们待在这
You guys stay here.
如果珍妮特来了
Oh, and, um, if Jeanette comes by,
千万别让她进来
do not let her into the apartment.
别让她进来  收到
Don't let her in. Got it.
伙计们  我是认真的  这女的就跟臭虫一样
Guys, this is serious. This girl is like bedbugs.
一旦进来了  赶都赶不走啊
Once she's in the apartment, there's no getting her out.
泰德老兄
Ted, buddy,
我们一起合力对付
how long have we been dealing with
巴尼的疯女友们多少年了  好多年了吧
Barney's insane girlfriends? Years.
历时近十年
Nigh on a decade!
我都五度出席听证会  指证被告精神失常
I had to testify in five competency hearings.
我认为我们对付珍妮特绰绰有余
I think we can handle Jeanette.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
回见
See you soon.
嫩着呢  是吧
That kid. Am I right?
肯定是忘了带钥匙了
Now look who forgot his keys.
是谁
What is it?
与此同时  莉莉和罗宾去外面吃午饭
Meanwhile, Lily and Robin were out getting lunch,
一场灾难降临了
when disaster struck.
天啊  我把他的奶嘴落公车上了
Oh, God, I left his binky on that bus!
等等  你没有其他奶嘴了吗
Wait. Don't you have other binkies?
那是他最爱的奶嘴  他分辨得出来
That one's his favorite! He'll know the difference!
我不会让他因为这事
I'm not gonna let this be the reason
而记恨我一辈子
he resents me later in life!
他一哭  就把他抱起来
If he starts crying, just pick him up!
什么
What? Uh, uh...
好好  不哭  不哭  乖乖
Okay, okay. Yeah, there, there, there. Okay.
我回来了  有发生什么事吗
Hey, I'm back. Did I miss anything?
没有
Nope.
珍妮特来过吗
Did Jeanette come by?
哪个珍妮特  我认识好多珍妮特
Jeanette? I know lots of Jeanettes.
伙计们
Guys!
好吧  她来过  她把书落这了
Okay, she came by because she forgot her book.
于是我们让她进你房间拿了
So we let her go up in your room and get it.
然后呢
And then?
然后什么
And then what?
然后她走了吗
And then she left?
我想她走了吧
I think she left.
你确定她走了吗
Are you sure she left?
我...
I am...
90%确信她走了
90% sure... that she left.
80%
80 percent.
事实上  我要重新回答这个问题
Actually, I'm gonna change my answer.
我现在觉得她没走
I am now starting to think she never left,
而且她还把自己关在你的房间了
and instead she barricaded herself in your room.
我永远都不会出来的
And I'm never coming out!
百分百确定了
A hundred percent.
你们俩不是吧
I cannot believe you guys!
谁让你事先没提醒过我们她是疯妹子
Well, maybe if you had given us a warning that she was crazy!
兄弟  没事啦
Dude, it's okay.
她不可能永远待在里面的
She can't stay in there forever.
她总得出来吃喝啊
She'll have to come out to eat and drink
或者上厕所  对吧
and go to the bathroom, right?
几个月以前
Now, a few months earlier,
东海岸曾遭到暴风雨袭击
the East Coast had been hit by a bad storm,
于是某些聪明过人  富有远见的纽约人
and some intelligent, forward-thinking New Yorkers
视其为醒世警钟
took it as a wake-up call,
确保自己卧室里储存了
making sure to stock their bedrooms
足够维持好几个月的食物和饮用水
with enough food and water to last months,
当然还有一个便携式排泄物处理装置
not to mention a portable waste management system.
这些措施实在是聪明之举
It was really the smart thing to do.
你个大呆瓜
You dumbass!
真的  泰德  你怎么能笨到如此不可救药呢
Really, Ted. How could you be so unbelievably stupid?
才怪  是你们笨蛋把
No, no, you guys are the ones
那个吸血魔女请到我卧室的
who invited a vampire into my apartment!
这都是你们的错
This is your fault!
随带一提  如果今天我们遇到是超强暴风雨
And P.S., if this disaster had been a superstorm
而不是什么性感女魔头
instead of a hot lunatic,
你们俩绝对会苦苦哀求  要我给冷冻蛋白酱吃
you'd all be begging to eat my freeze-dried protein paste
要我给生化垃圾桶排便
and crap in my biohazard bucket. Just sayin'.
我找到了
I got it.
落在公车的地板上了
It was on the floor of the bus.
我应该直接丢掉算了
I should probably throw it out.
他没出什么问题吧
Did he give you any problems?
小小哭了一下  然后就没事了
He cried a little, but then he stopped.
太好了  没出其他什么事吧
Oh, good. Anything else happen?
没有
Nope.
仅此而已
That... is... it.
4年后
喝光了
All gone!
我们真该经常这样
We have to do this more often.
完全同意
Oh, we totally do.
真不敢相信马文都读幼儿园了
I can't believe Marvin's in kindergarten.
他长得可真快啊
He's growing up so fast.
我可以向你坦白一件事吗
Can I confess something to you?
还记得你把马文的奶嘴忘在巴士上
Remember the day you left Marvin's binky on the bus
-然后让我独自照顾马文的那次吗  -记得
- and you left me alone with him? - Yeah.
我当时没敢把这事告诉你  不过...
Well, I didn't tell you this at the time, but...
好了好了  不哭不哭
Okay, okay. Yeah, there, there, there.
乖乖
Okay, shh, shh.
看来某人很不开心啊
Oh, no, it looks like somebody's not happy.
真的  我超不爽的
No kidding. I'm miserable.
他怎么能哭成这样
Listen to this thing.
他大概只是想要人抱抱吧
He probably just wants to be held.
你说得对
I think you're right.
-你能抱抱他吗  -当然
- Can you do it? - All right.
来让我抱抱  小帅哥
Come here, handsome.
乖乖
Oh. Yeah. Yes.
我让一个陌生人抱了马文  对不起
I let a stranger pick up Marvin. I'm sorry.
我当时没有亲自抱他
It's just, I hadn't actually picked him up at that point,
我吓坏了  所以...
and I was scared, so...
算了吧  都四年以前的事了
You know what? It was four years ago.
他现在茁壮成长  所以别担心这个了
He's obviously fine. Don't even worry about it.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
反正除此之外  没别的事发生了吧
I mean, as long as there's not more to that story.
没有
Nope.
仅此而已
That... is... it.
珍妮特  你得离开
Jeanette, you have to leave!
马上  我还没找到我的书呢
In a minute! I still haven't found that book!
听着  珍妮特  我不想做到这个份上
Listen, Jeanette, I didn't want to do this,
但我已经报警了  警察马上就到
but I called the police. They're on their way.
各小组注意  各小组注意
All units, all units.
521号西街82幢15户需要出警
Possible 10-90 in progress at 521 West 82nd, apartment 15.
这声音是从哪儿来的
Where's that coming from?
-是你吗  德罗丽斯  -珍妮特
- Is that you, Dolores? - Jeanette?
妹子  最近过得如何啊
Hey, girl. How you been?
还是原来的老样子啦
Oh, you know, I'm just doing me.
总之  我会去查看那个地址的
Anyway, I'll check out that 10-90.
好的  不过要记住...
Okay, but remember...
我知道  不要过度使用暴力
I know, no excessive force.
我不想要再被停职查看了  对吧
Last thing I need is another suspension, am I right?
孩子们  那个时候我才发现
And that, kids, was how I found out
珍妮特的职业原来是警察
what Jeanette did for a living.
珍妮特・彼得森中尉
等一下
Wait a second.
她是条子吗
Is she a cop?!
我看她是条子哦
I think she's a cop!
你早就知道她是条子了
Did you know she was a cop?!
我根本不知道她是个条子[《无间行者》的哏]
I didn't know she was a cop!
泰德  抱歉地通知你
Ted, I'm sorry I have to say this--
这里现在是珍妮特的家了  是她的地盘
Jeanette lives here now. This is her place.
-你赶快离开吧  -什么
- You're gonna have to leave. - What?
那你们怎么不离开呢
Why don't you have to leave?
他们可以留下来
They can stay.
-谢了  珍妮特警官  -谢了  珍妮特警官
- Thank you, Officer Jeanette. - Thank you, Officer Jeanette.
12年后
又喝完了
All gone.
我们真该经常这样
We need to do this more often.
完全同意  真不敢相信马文已经上初中了
We totally do. I can't believe marvin's in middle school.
他长得可真快啊
Oh, he's growing up so fast.
我可以向你坦白一件事吗
Can I confess something to you?
还记得你把马文的奶嘴忘在巴士上
Remember that day you left Marvin's binky on the bus
然后我让个陌生老太太抱他的事吗
and I let that old lady pick him up?
我记得事情应该就这么简单吧
I seem to recall that was the entire story.
其实我还剩一点没说完
There's a little bit more.
不哭不哭  小乖乖
There, there, little one.
我把你放回你的小车车
Let's put you back in your strolly-poo,
这样你就能慢慢飘向梦梦园
so you can drift off to dreamy-dreamy land.
真是太谢谢你了
Oh, thank you so much.
这是我第一次和他单独在一起
Yeah, this is my first time alone with him,
我一直忐忑不安  觉得我会
and, you know, um, I have this weird feeling that I'm gonna,
我会把他掉地下  或是害他受伤
I don't know, like, drop him or injure him in some way,
我可真是杞人忧天
which is completely insane.
-不过  -天啊
- But... - Oh, heavens.
妈呀
Oh, my God!
我的天呀
Oh, my God.
我真的真的很抱歉
I know, I'm so sorry.
算了
Well, you know what?
那已经是12年前的事了
That was what, 12 years ago?
别为这事担心了
Don't even worry about it.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
答应我  除此之外没其他事情发生了吧
Just promise me there's no more to that story.
没有  仅此而已
Nope, that is it.
你真的要这么做吗
Are you sure you want to do this?
那姑娘可是警察呢
The girl's a cop.
真的  这主意看起来很不妙
Yeah, this seems like a really bad idea.
我不管了
I don't care.
我要冲进我的卧室
I am going into that bedroom
因为这里是我家
because this is my home
我必须拼死保卫它
and I have to defend it.
但最主要的原因是
But mostly because
人家的抗过敏药都放在里面呢
my allergy medication is in there!
好吧  总之一切小心  好吗
All right, just be careful, okay?
那个姑娘真是个疯妹子
This girl is really crazy.
对啊  她怎么就不能接受
Yeah, why can't she just accept
你们分手的事实呢
the fact that you guys broke up?
我也觉得  她怎么就不能好好接受呢
I know, I know, why can't she just accept that?
为什么  到底是为什么啊
Why, it's, like, why?
也许是因为我们其实还没有分手吧
It might be because we didn't actually break up.
拜托  珍妮特  那可是我的珍藏黑胶唱片啊
Aw, man. Jeanette, come on, that's vintage vinyl.
泰德  昨天晚上你到底有没有
Ted, did you or didn't you break up
和珍妮特分手
with Jeanette last night?
我不知道  状况有点混乱
I don't know, it's kind of confusing.
我们需要谈一谈
I think we need to talk.
哦  好呀
Oh, oh, okay.
我知道你要说什么了
I see where this is going.
你爱上了莉莉是吧
You're in love with Lily.
你是要说这个吧  对不对
That's it, isn't it?
什么  不  我
What? No, I...
想到她光鲜的医学文凭和性感的南方口音
Like I should be surprised with her fancy medical degree
我早就该料到了
and her sexy Southern drawl.
什么  她不是...
What? She's not...
别跟我说话  别看我
Don't talk to me, don't look at me.
我恨你  我再也不要见到你了
I hate you and I never want to see you again!
接下来的事一发不可收拾
And then things got crazy
我们被赶出了巴克莱中心
and we got thrown out of the Barclays Center.
我觉得这就算是分手了吧
I don't know, it felt pretty breakup-y.
总之
Anyway,
当时我们不欢而散  所以...
we parted on pretty bad terms, so...
我以为也许我可以借此...
I kind of thought maybe I could...
再不和她联系  希望她能意识到这点
Never contact her again and hope she'd take the hint
从此再也不来打扰你吗
and just leave you alone?
巴尼  别把我想得这么烂
Barney, give me some credit.
-那这是你的计划吗  -正是
- Was that the plan? - Yes.
14年后
-喝完了  -我们真该经常这样
- All gone. - We need to do this more often.
完全同意
We totally do.
真不敢相信马文都读高中了
I can't believe Marvin's in high school.
他长得可真快啊
He's growing up so fast.
-我可以向你坦白一件事吗  -又来了  什么事
- Can I confess something to you? - Oh, no. What?
到底发生了什么事
What happened?
告诉我你把我儿子到底怎么了
Tell me what you did to my son.
真是太不顺利了
This is not going well at all.
亲爱的  你浑身发抖
Oh, honey, you are shaking.
咱们找个暖和的地方
Let's get you out of the cold.
这附近有什么店吗
What's open near here?
你带着我家婴儿去脱衣舞俱乐部了
You took my infant child to a strip club?
只是露两点而已
It was just topless.
反正他在家也老看你的啊
He saw yours all the time anyway.
好了  对不起  我不该带他去那里
Okay, I'm sorry, I shouldn't have done that,
但全部经过就是这样
but that is all there is.
真的没有什么要补充的了
Okay, there is no more to the story.
我把全部经过都告诉你了
I have now told you everything.
16年后
喝光了
All gone.
我们真该经常这样
We need to do this more often.
完全同意  真不敢相信马文已经会开车了
We totally do. I can't believe Marvin's driving.
他长得可真快啊
He's growing up so fast.
-好吧  还有一件事  -又怎么了
- Okay, there's one other thing. - What?
我得去下洗手间
Well, I have to go use the ladies' room.
你能帮我照看他一下吗
Can you watch him for me?
当然没问题
Of course.
真想把你一口吞下去
I could just eat you up.
你把他交给一个完全陌生的人
You left him with a complete stranger?
他可能被...
He could've been...
罗宾  你怎么能这样
Robin, how could you?
莉莉  拜托  这是16年前的事了
Lily, please, okay, it was 16 years ago.
他没事
He's fine.
你说的对
You're right.
没事
It's fine.
老天  能彻底坦白的感觉真是太好了
God, it feels so good to have gotten this off my chest.
我终于鼓足勇气说出一切
Finally it is all on the table.
所有秘密都坦白了
All secrets are exposed
再也没有好隐瞒的了
and there is nothing left to be revealed.
17年后
-又喝光了  -我们真该经常...
- All gone.  We need to do this more...
-其实我还没说完  -见鬼  罗宾
- There's more to the story. - Damn it, Robin.
你到底还有什么没告诉我
What could you possibly have left out?
只是有
It's just there's, um,
一个小细节  我稍微修改了一下
one little detail that I may have slightly altered.
如果他哭  就把他抱起来
If he starts crying, just pick him up.
乖乖  别哭
Yeah, there, there.
配合点  小家伙
Come on, buddy, shh.
看来有人不开心啊
Looks like somebody's unhappy.
真的  我超不爽的
No kidding, I'm miserable.
他怎么能哭成这样
Listen to this thing.
他大概只是想要人抱抱吧
Maybe he needs to be held.
你说得对
I think you're right.
你能抱抱他吗
Can you do it?
当然
Sure.
过来  小帅哥
Come here, handsome.
过来过来  你这个帅气的小家伙
Come here, come here, you handsome devil, you.
你长得真漂亮啊
You're such a beautiful...
真是个酷小伙
Aw, you're such a cool dude.
瞧你
Oh, look at you, oh.
好了  乖了不哭  小家伙  乖乖
All right, there, there, little one, there, there.
我把你放回你的小车车
Let me put you back in your strolly-poo
这样你就能慢慢飘向梦梦园
so you can drift off to dreamy-dreamy land.
好吗  好了
Okay? All right.
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
别客气
Hey, don't worry about it.
这是我第一次单独和他在一起
It's my first time alone with him,
我一直忐忑不安
and I just have this weird feeling
觉得我会把他掉地下  或是害他受伤
I'm gonna drop him or injure him in some way.
我可真是杞人忧天
I know it's completely insane...
我的天  小心  不好
Oh, heavens, oh, watch it, no!
不
No!
真是太不顺利了
This is not going well at all.
亲爱的  你浑身发抖
Oh, hon, you're shaking.
咱们找个暖和的地方
Let's get out of the cold.
这附近有什么店吗
Is there anything open near here?
我得去下洗手间
Hey, I need to go to the ladies' room--
你能帮我照看他一下吗
can you watch him for me?
当然没问题  真想把你一口吞下去
Of course. I could just eat you up.
瞧你  怎么这样可耐  好可耐
Look at you, yum, yum, yum, yum.
你隐瞒了17年才告诉我
You waited 17 years to tell me
你曾经碰到了史上最伟大的拳击手
that you met the greatest boxer of all time?
我的儿子曾经被参议员迈克・泰森哄睡着
My son was rocked to sleep by Senator Mike Tyson?
-我想告诉你的  相信我  -你怎么能这样
- I wanted to tell you, believe me. - How could you...?
正确的做法是
Okay, this is the right thing to do.
你上楼去  真正和她分手
You got to go up there and break up with her for real.
别担心  如果有事
And don't worry, if anything happens,
尖叫就行  我们会去救你的
just scream, we'll come rescue you.
好的
Okay.
5分钟后
你们没听到我在上面尖叫吗
Did you guys not hear me screaming up there?
我觉得好内疚
Aw, I feel so awful.
我们去买赛百味三明治了
We went to get subs.
不过给你也买了一个
We got you one though.
我们没有给你买
We didn't get you one.
这么说你的房间被珍妮特霸占了
So, Jeanette's squatting in your room?
你们怎么来了
What are you guys doing here?
我们在三条街外听到你尖叫
We heard you screaming from three blocks away.
她为什么在房间里
Why is she in there?
莉莉  没有什么"为什么"
Lily, there is no reason why.
这就像问地球为什么是圆的
That's like asking why is the earth round?
为什么早上会出太阳
Why does the sun come up in the morning?
我为什么要工作
What do I do for a living?
有些问题就是注定不该知道答案的
There are some questions we're not meant to know the answer to.
疯妹子是疯子  是因为她们本来就疯
Crazy girls are crazy because they're crazy.
我不认为这么简单
I-I don't think it's quite that simple.
我跟一个朋友说了泰德和珍妮特的事
I was talking to a friend of mine about Ted and Jeanette.
有没搞错  什么朋友
Oh, great, what friend is this?
我认识的一个充满智慧的老太太
Uh, just this wise old lady that I know.
疯狂其实是因为
Here's the thing about crazy.
当一个男的发送模棱两可的信号给妹子时
When a guy sends mixed signals to a girl,
会给她的心理健康造成伤害
it takes a toll on her psychological well-being.
想知道妹子为什么会发疯
You want to know why a girl acts crazy,
瞧她的男朋友就明白了
look at the guy she's dating.
你会看到什么叫真正的疯狂
Then you really see some crazy.
相信我
Trust me.
你是迈克・泰森吗
Are you Mike Tyson?
慢着
Now, hold on.
我这辈子约会过数不清的疯妹子
I've dated tons of crazy girls in my life,
我每一次对待她们的方式是...
and not once have I ever treated them with anything other than...
对  我禽兽不如
Oh, right, I'm a monster.
也许脸上有纹身的老太太是对的
Maybe the old lady with the face tattoo is right.
也许珍妮特会这样的原因
Maybe the reason Jeanette's acting this way
就是泰德
is Ted.
我  怎么成了我的错了
Me? How is this my fault?
就是  这可是泰德
Yeah, come on, this is Ted we're talking about.
我相信他没有做什么事误导她
I'm sure he didn't do anything to lead her on
或是发送模棱两可的信号  对吧  泰德
or send mixed signals, right, Ted?
别跟我说话  别看我
Don't talk to me, don't look at me.
我恨你  我再也不想看到你了
I hate you and I never want to see you again!
然后我们被赶出了巴克利中心
And we got thrown out of the Barclays Center.
好吧  我失望了
Okay, that's disappointing.
太失望了
So disappointing.
对啊
Seriously.
但那是昨晚的事了  又不是说...
But that was last night. I mean, it's not like...
听着  珍妮特 我们得
Listen, Jeanette, we really need to
认真谈谈我们的事
have a serious talk about our...
这双靴子是莉莉留在这里的吗
So, did Lily leave these boots here
还是其他贱女人啊
or was it some other bitch?
马修  巴尼  救命
Marshall, Barney, help me!
我想他们不会上来了
I don't think they're coming.
我想也是
I guess not.
都怪那双红靴子
It's those red boots.
谁穿上都是那么性感撩人
They just look sexy on everyone.
泰德  你对这双红靴子有什么情结啊
Okay, Ted, what is with the red boots?
你是个聪明人  你有品味
You're a smart guy, you've got some taste,
你长了眼睛
you got a visual sense, I mean,
你可是个建筑师啊
you're an architect for Pete's sakes.
你怎么能看着那双靴子然后觉得...
How can you look at those boots and think...
我的天  我抱着他  我抱着宝宝
Oh, my God, I'm holding it, I'm holding the baby.
你从来没抱过他吗
What, you've never held him before?
抱过无数次了好吧
Uh, tons of times.
这对我来说可不是什么重大时刻
This-this is not a big moment for me.
太令人激动了
This is exhilarating.
好了  我知道你要说什么
Look, yes, I know what you're gonna say.
我必须和她分手
I have to break up with her.
不  我准备说相反的话
No, I was actually gonna say the opposite.
我认为你现在应该和珍妮特在一起
I think you need to be with Jeanette right now.
因为她就是我的真命天女
Because she's the one.
不  怎么会  绝对不是
No. What? No.
她是个疯子
She's insane.
但我认为现在你也有点疯
But I think you are also a little insane right now.
你应该和你的疯妹子约会一段时间
So I think you need to go be with your crazy girl for a while
然后等到一切热情燃烧殆尽时
and when it all goes down in flames--
我不是在打比方
and I don't mean that figuratively,
我盼望着能真的有一场熊熊大火
I expect there to be actual flames...
还真被她说中了
And there were.
我们会陪着你的  因为我们爱你
...we'll be here for you because we love you.
珍妮特  我想说
Jeanette I just want to say that, uh,
你这样乱翻乱砸我的东西
you going through my stuff like that...
你真的很特别
You are really something special.
我会给莉莉寄一只死动物
I'm gonna send Lily a dead animal in the mail.
我想我真的喜欢上你了
I think I'm falling for you.
我认为我们应该和我的心理医生玩3P
I think we should have a three-way with my therapist.
他70岁了
He's 70.
你戴几号的戒指
What is your ring size?
罗宾
Robin.
已经凌晨三点了
It's 3:00 in the morning.
真的吗
Really?
对  你要不要把他
Yeah, you sure you don't want to just
放进婴儿床  然后回家休息
put him in the crib and, you know, go home?
不用  我没事
No, I'm good.
好吧
Okay.
晚安
Good night.
那是什么味道
What's that smell?
莉莉  莉莉
Lily! Lily!